pesn.com 2016-10-12

# Privacy Policy of Pure Energy Systems

**Approved by PES Network, Inc. Board of Directors June 7, 2004**

We take your privacy seriously. PES Network, Inc. (PES) has created this policy in order to demonstrate our concern and commitment to your privacy. PES does not sell any private information it collects.

### PES GATHERING AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION 

**COOKIES**

As of April 8, 2009, our Google AdSense advertising service will collect information on users in order to provide interest-based advertising.  This allows advertisers to show ads based on a user's previous interactions with them, such as visits to advertiser website and also to reach users based on their interests.  PES itself does not collect or use user-specific data on visitors to our site except for online forms through which users submit information, such as our news submission page, or NEC member application page, which collect the users IP address.

**Registration for PESWiki**

We request that you use your real name on your profile page, and we recommend that you also include your email.  You can cloak your email from spambots by formatting it something like this: <emailname {at} domain.com>.  Presently we are manually setting up user accounts, due to previously problems with spam submissions.  In applying for a user account, you will be given an option as to what additional information you wish to include in your profile page.  Information you wish to be kept private will be kept private.  We request this information so that we can contact you in the case of any issues that may arise with content you post/modify at PESWiki.

**Registration for Email Lists**

PES presently uses Yahoo Groups for specific project e-mail lists.  Yahoo Groups requires users to provide contact and other information.  PES does not have access to the private portions of this information, such as address and password.  That is administered by Yahoo Groups.

**PRIVATE Project Lists**

PES sets up and moderates password protected lists using Yahoo Groups at this time. However, in some rare cases, protected lists may become public. Participants will be informed when the list is to be made public and have the option to request that Pure Energy Systems remove any information they do not want made public.

**PUBLIC Lists**

PES sets up and moderates public lists using Yahoo Groups. Information disclosed on public lists is considered public information and may appear on the website as well as in the list archives. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these areas.

**Changes to this Policy**

This Privacy Policy may change over time. Data collected can and will be used in accordance with the posted Privacy Policy at the time of collection. Changes to this policy are not retroactive. Pure Energy Systems reserves the right to modify the policy at any time. Please check this page periodically to see if any changes have been made. Changes become effective upon posting modified Privacy Policy.

**3** **rd** **Party Privacy**

PES websites contains advertisements from third parties. We also use Yahoo Groups to handle our project lists. The website may also contain hyperlinks to third party websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such third parties. Please check with those sites to determine their privacy policies.

###

**Contact  
****email:** <[legal {at} pureenergysystems.com](mailto:legal@pureenergysystems.com?subject=PES%20Privacy%20Statement) >  
**PES Network, Inc.**  
4157 N. West Pinion Cir., Eagle Mountain UT 840005, USA  
**Ph:** 801-407-1292  
**Fax:** 801-880-8322

Posted by SDA June 8, 2004  
Last updated December 24, 2014
